Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.2
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 2 Locals, 2.
  - Local 255
    - Local 255 Newspaper Clippings, October 7, 1946-June 15, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - "Pittsfield Union Demands Recall of Two Leaders" Springfield Union, February 25, 1949; 5.
      - "Draftsmen End Strike, IUE Also Accepts Raise", June 15, 1953; 6.
      - "GE Drops German for Slurring Flag", 7.
      - "UE Here Anti Smith Likewise" Springfield Union, 8.
      - "GE is Blamed by Matles for Plants BIO Jobless" Springfield Union, 9.
      - "Rotary Club's Knowledge of CIO Not Increase", 10.
      - "All Those Who Don't Care Raise Their Right Hand", 11.
      - "Pittsfield UE Local Sets Right Up on Hind Legs" Springfield Union, 12.
  - Local 256
    - Local 256 Affairs Lists, December 1942-March 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Local 256 Incoming Correspondence, September 22, 1941-June 17, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Julius Emspak to J. Gontarz Regarding Local 256 Officers and Mailing List, September 22, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Gontarz Regarding Finances, October 27, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Mollie Schultz Regarding Dues and Local 256 Constitutions, April 23, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Schultz Regarding Finances, July 19, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Schultz Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 10, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Samuel Russell Regarding Political Action Committee, October 17, 1947-April 6, 1948; 6-13.
      - Nat Geller to Gontarz Regarding Supplies, November 12, 1941; 14.
      - Charles Rivers to Gontarz Regarding Dues, Women and Local 256 Constitutions, January 10, 1942; 15.
      - David Scribner to Schultz Regarding Dues Check-off, June 17, 1948; 16.
    - Local 256 Outgoing Correspondence, September 22, 1941-May 18, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Mary Dubnansky to Julius Emspak Regarding United Steelworkers of America, Andrew Terry and Cooper Oven, May 26, 1943; 1.
      - Jeanne Dukeley to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, March 22, 1943; 2.
      - Joseph Gontarz to UE Regarding Mailing List with October, 1941, Gontarz Letter to UE Regarding Local 256 Officers on Back and Gontarz Letter to Emspak, September 22, 1941; 3.
      - Gontarz to Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 23, 1941; 4.
      - Gontarz to UE Regarding Dues and Women, October 26, 1941; 5.
      - Gontarz to Emspak Regarding Local 256 Reconstitutes Women Dues, November 10, 1941; 6.
      - Samuel Russell to UE Regarding Political Action Committee, October 1947; 7.
      - Russell to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 5-12, 1947; 8-9.
      - Mollise Schultz to UE Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 2, 1945; 10.
      - Schultz to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, May 18, 1950; 11.
      - Unsigned Letter to UE Regarding PAC, October 13, 1947; 12.
    - Local 256 Salary and Expense Letters, Olga Sosidko, October 6, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Local 256 UE News, May 2-7, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Mollie Schultz to Julius Emspak, May 2, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Schultz, May 7, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Charles Rivers, May 7, 1941; 3.
    - Local 256 Womens Dues, October 31, 1941-April 2, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Julius Emspak to Charles Rivers, October 31-November 27, 1941; 1-2.
      - Joseph Gontarz to Emspak, December 29, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Rivers, January 8, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Gontarz, January 8, 1942; 5.
      - Martin Hourihan to Emspak, February 18, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak Secretary to Hourihan, February 19, 1942; 7.
      - Hourihan to Stella Abrams, February 20, 1942; 8.
      - Rivers to Emspak, March 3, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak to Hourihan, March 5, 1942; 10.
      - Emspak to Rivers, April 2, 1942; 11.
    - Local 256 vs. Terryville Lock Company, December 30, 1949-May 27, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Local 256 Financial Correspodnence, Connecticut UE Locals with October 9, 1941, Julius Emspak Letter to Joseph Gontarz (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Local 256 Leaflets, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Statement by the Executive Board of Local 256 Regarding Factionalism and Local 203, July 1947; 1.
      - Statement on Hartford Seccession Movement Regarding Factionalism and Local 203, 1947; 2.
  - Local 257
    - Local 257 Officers Lists, March 16, 1944-August 18, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Local 257 Incoming Correspondence, November 8, 1940-April 6, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Julius Emspak to Louis D'Entremont Regarding Mailing List, November 8, 1940; 1.
      - Emspak to D'Entremont Regarding Finances with Bonding Questionnaire and July 1, 1941, Emspak Letter to David Rosston, December 23, 1940; 2.
      - Emspak to Albert McCarthy Regarding Mailing List, February 19, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Paul Davis Regarding Finances, October 6, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Davis Regarding Local 257 Wire Products Collective Bargaining, November 7, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Lawrence Jenkins, April 2, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to W.C. Budden, December 10, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Wilfred Bugden Regarding Contracts and Local 257 Wire Products, December 29, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Bugden, January 8, 1943; 9.
      - Emspak to Joseph Power Regarding Foremen, February 23, 1943; 10.
      - Emspak to Rita Buzas Regarding Eagle Lock, May 26, 1943; 11.
      - Emspak to Donald Miller Regarding Veterans and Dues, August 22, 1943; 12.
      - Emspak to Anthony Benedetto Regarding Local 257 Wire Products Strikes and Organizations, February 11, 1947; 13.
      - Emspak Telegram to J.L. Powers Regarding Local 257 Wire Products Collective Bargaining, February 25, 1946; 14.
      - Emspak to Benedetto, June 18, 1947; 15.
      - Emspak Secretary to Leonard Hummrich Regarding E.W. Pitman Strikes, January 21, 1948; 16.
      - Emspak to Donald Miller Regarding Political Action Committee, February 19-April 6, 1948; 17-19.
      - Frederick Livingston to David Bennett Regarding Taxation, May 2, 1944; 20.
      - James Matles Telegram to Wilbur Stickney Regarding Metropolitan Retail Wholesale Department Store Employees Union Strikes, December 5, 1941; 21.
      - Matles Secretary to Wilbur Stickney Regarding Local 257 Wire Products Collective Bargaining, April 1, 1942; 22.
    - Local 257 Outgoing Correspondence, December 23, 1940-June 12, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Anthony Benedetto to UE Regarding Supplies, February 5, 1946; 1.
      - Benedetto to James Matles Regarding Wire Products Collective Bargaining, July 22, 1947; 2.
      - Wilfred Bugden to Julius Emspak Regarding Closed Shop, Part-time Workers and Seniority with Amendments to Contract, December 6, 1942; 3.
      - Bugden to Emspak Regarding Grievances, December 18, 1942; 4.
      - Bugden Telegram to Emspak Regarding Grievances, January 4, 1943; 5.
      - Rita Buzas to Emspak Regarding Local 257 Officers, January 10, 1942; 6.
      - Paul Davis to UE Regarding Local 257 Officers, September 28, 1941; 7.
      - Davis to UE Regarding Wire Products and Wages, October 2, 1941; 8.
      - Davis to Emspak Regarding Local 257 Wire Products Collective Bargaining and Arbitrations, October 25, 1941; 9.
      - Louis D'Entremont to UE Regarding Finances, December 23, 1940; 10.
      - Paul Hoffman to UE Regarding Finances, November 2, 1943; 11.
      - Hoffman to Emspak Regarding Local 257 Officers, March 6, 1944; 12.
      - Leonard Hummrich to Emspak Regarding Local 257 E.W. Pitman Strikes, January 19, 1948; 13.
      - Lawrence Jenkins to Emspak Regarding Local 257 Officers, February 23, 1942; 14.
      - Jenkins to Emspak Regarding Wages and Local 257 Wire Products Collective Bargaining, March 29, 1942; 15.
      - William McKenna to UE Regarding Local 257 Officers, February 9-March 16, 1944; 16-17.
      - Donald Muller to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Closed-shop Dues, August 21, 1945; 18.
      - Muller to Political Action Committee Regarding PAC, February 2, 1948; 19.
      - Muller to UE Regarding Local 257 E.W. Pitman Signal Manufacturing Strikes and North Shore Cutting Die, June 12, 1948; 20.
    - Local 257 Outgoing Correspondence, December 6, 1941-February 16, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Joseph Power to Julius Emspak Regarding Foremen, February 16, 1948; 1.
      - Powers Telegram to UE Regarding Local 257 Wire Products Collective Bargaining, February 25, 1946; 2.
      - Wilbur Stickney Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Metropolitan Wire Strikes, December 1941; 3.
      - Stickney Telegram to James Matles Regarding Metropolitan Wire, December 6, 1941; 4.
      - Stickney to Matles Regarding Local 257 Wire Products Collective Bargaining, March 31, 1942; 5.
    - Local 257 Bonding Form, July 14, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Local 257 Staff Assistance, October 4-December 10, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Wilfred Bugden to Julius Emspak, October 4, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Donald Towey, October 6, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Richard Linsley, December 10, 1942; 3.
    - Local 257 North Shore Cutting Die War Labor Board Case, July 30-October 15, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - J. L. Powers Telegram to UE, July 30, 1943; 1.
      - James Matles Telegram to Richard Linsley, July 30, 1941; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Jack Simon, October 7, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to William McKenna, October 15, 1943; 4.
    - Local 257 Globe Machine Financial Report, December 14-15, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - David bennett to A.N. Towsen, December 14, 1943; 1.
      - Townsen to Bennett, December 15, 1943; 2.
    - Local 257 Audit, April 9-26, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Julius Emspak to H. F. Tuxbury, April 9, 1945; 1.
      - Tuxbury to Emspak, April 16, 1945; 2.
      - Ray Klausner to Richard Linsley, April 17, 1945; 3.
      - Linsley to Klausner, April 26, 1945; 4.
    - Local 257 North Shore Cutting Die Strike, May 28-June 11, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Julius Emspak to Paul Seymour, May 28, 1946; 1.
      - Helen Lief to Don Tormey, June 8, 1946; 2.
      - Tormey to Lief, June 11, 1946; 3.
    - Local 257 Lamp Industry Mailings, October 1-23, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Anthony Benedetto to Ben Riskin, October 1, 1946; 1.
      - Riskin to Benedetto, October 23, 1946; 2.
    - Local 257 Health Care Plans, September 23-October 16, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Anthony Benedetto to Janet Barish, September 23, 1946; 1.
      - Barish to Benedetto, October 15, 1946; 2.
      - Benedetto to Barish, October 16, 1946; 3.
    - Local 257 J.C. Pitman Collective Bargaining and Factionalism, May 6-June 18, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, May 6, 1947; 1.
      - John O'Donnell to Paul Seymour with Petition, June 2, 1947; 2.
      - Althony Benedetto to General Executive Board, June 12, 1947; 3.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Seymour, June 18, 1947; 4.
    - Local 257 Political Action Committee Receipts, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 25-26)
    - Local 257 Dues Increase, June-July 1948 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Paul Hauffman to UE, June 1948; 1.
      - Membership Meeting Notice, June 8, 1948; 2.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Don Tormey with June 1948, Hoffman Letter to UE, July 2, 1948; 3.
    - Local 257 North Shore Cutting Die Signal Manufacturing Strikes, June 10-November 26, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Joseph Torkowski Telegram to Anthony Benedetto, June 10, 1948; 1.
      - Nat Spero to Don Tormey, November 24, 1948; 2.
      - Tormey to Spero, November 26, 1948; 3.
    - Local 257 Bonding, May 16-June 7, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Donald Muller to UE, May 16, 1949; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Muller, June 7, 1949; 2.
    - Local 257 Correspondence and Strike Termination Notice, October 6, 1941-November 12, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Julius Emspak to Richard Linsley, October 6, 1941; 1.
      - Paul Hoffman to UE Regarding Northeast Die Organization, May 1943; 2.
      - Termination of Strike Notice, November 12, 1946; 3.
  - Local 258
    - Local 258 Officers Lists, February 23, 1944-January 27, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Local 258 Incoming Correspondence, April 15, 1941-October 18, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - William Chapman to Frank LaRonca Regarding Decca Conference, January 11, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Umberto Scippa Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1949; 2.
      - Emspak to Rowena Paomi Regarding Supplies, April 15, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Steve Zielinski Regarding Transfers, December 5, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Walter Rozyski Regarding Finances, September 30-December 27, 1946; 5-6.
      - Emspak to Rozycki Regarding Political Action Committee, December 9, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Rozycki, May 12, 1948; 8.
      - Emspak to Irene Papp Regarding UE News Bridgeport, May 27, 1949; 9.
      - James Matles to LaRonca, June 12, 1941; 10.
      - Matles to Scippa Regarding Finances, February 3, 1942; 11.
    - Local 258 Outgoing Correspondence, April 1941-November 1952 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Frances Bennett to Julius Emspak Regarding Anniversary Banquet, February 16, 1945; 1.
      - Irene Papp to UE Regarding Political Action Committee, December 1947; 2.
      - Papp to UE Regarding Supplies, May 1948; 3.
      - Rowena Paumi to Emspak Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization Youth Association and Supplies, April 1941; 4.
      - Paumi to UE Regarding Local 258 Office, November 4, 1941; 5.
      - Paumi to James Matles Regarding Decca Collective Bargaining, January 28, 1944; 6.
      - Paumi to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 258 Officers, February 1944; 7.
      - Paumi to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 3, 1944; 8.
      - John Pohl to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strikes, November 20, 1952; 9.
      - Walter Rozycki to UE Regarding Finances, December 18, 1946; 10.
    - Local 258 Correspondence, May 27, 1968-August 22, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Local 258 Salary and Expense Letters, Umberto Scippa, December 26, 1940-December 1, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Local 258 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, June 24, 1968-June 6, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Local 258 Siemon Closing, August 1-23, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Harry Kaplan Report Excerpt, August 1, 1954; 1.
      - Richard Linsley to Julius Emspak, August 23, 1954; 2.
    - Local 258 Windsor Cone Automatic Machine Company, November 12, 1981-December 31, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Local 258 Legislative Committee and Political Action (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Local 259
    - Local 259 Officers Lists, February 4, 1942-March 10, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Local 259 Incoming Correspondence, February 17, 1942-April 19, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Julius Emspak to Raymond Richards Regarding Finances, February 17, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Albert Brunelle Regarding Bonus, February 26, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Raymond Richards Regarding Finances, March 15, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to John Cadbois Regarding Local 259 Constitutions, April 2, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Carlton Stiks Regarding Mine, Mill and Smelter Strikes, March 9, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Walter Felsentreger Regarding Supplies, July 8, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to Felsentreger Regarding Local 259 Newspaper, July 22, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Felsentreger Regarding Wages, Overtime and Unemployment, October 16, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak Telegram to William McLaughlin, January 13, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak to Charles Auslander Regarding Finances, March 24, 1943; 10.
      - Emspak to Auslander Regarding Dues, March 9, 1944; 11.
      - Emspak to Richard Gelinas Regarding Finances, March 21-May 2, 1944; 12-13.
      - Emspak to Casimir Tryba Regarding Veterans and Dues, October 29, 1945; 14.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Leon Massa, November 6, 1945; 15.
      - Emspak to Norman Savoie Regarding Finances, December 5, 1951; 16.
      - Emspak to Massa Regarding Supplies, Februray 21, 1952; 17.
      - Emspak to Stephan Sutton Regarding National Strike Fund, October 23, 1952; 18.
      - Emspak to William Rogers Regarding National Strike Fund, November 5, 1952; 19.
      - Emspak to Rogers Regarding Finances, April 15, 1953; 20.
      - Emspak to Sutton Regarding Finances, March 23-April 19, 1955; 21-22.
    - Local 259 Incoming Correspondence, October 17, 1941-April 19, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Nat Geller to Walter Felsentreger Regarding Finances, October 9, 1942; 1.
      - Geller Telegram to Felsentreger, November 9, 1942; 2.
      - James Matles to Albert Brunelle Regarding Local 259 Contracts, October 17, 1941; 3.
      - Matles to Carlton Stiles Regarding Cincinnati Worthington Pump, February 19, 1942; 4.
      - Matles to Stiles Regarding Productivity, February 25, 1942; 5.
      - Matles to Stiles, April 21, 1942; 6.
      - Matles to Stiles Regarding Local 259 Worthington Pump Collective Bargaining, War Labor Board and Membership Maintenance, June 4, 1942; 7.
      - Matles to Steve Sutton Regarding Readers Digest, National Labor Relations Board and Anti-communism, February 17, 1953; 8.
      - Matles to Leon Massa Regarding Arbitration, April 19, 1955; 9.
      - Russ Nixon to William Powers Regarding Poetry with Poem, September 4, 1947; 10.
      - Paul Seymour to Steve Sutton Regarding Arbitration, Februray 14, 1955; 11.
    - Local 259 Outgoing Correspondence, February 7, 1941-July 20, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Charles Auslander to James Matles Regarding Local 259 Contracts, March 30, 1943; 1.
      - Auslander to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 2, 1944; 2.
      - Auslander to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 31, 1944; 3.
      - Don Dollen Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 259 Koegels Machine Strikes, August 14, 1947; 4.
      - Albert Brunelle to Emspak Regarding Wages and Worthington Pump, February 7, 1941; 5.
      - Brunelle Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 259 Collective Bargaining, February 1941; 6.
      - Walter Felsentreger to Emspak Regarding Local Newspaper, July 1, 1942; 7.
      - Felsentreger to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Wages, July 7, 1942; 8.
      - Felsentreger to Emspak Regarding Local Newspaper with July 20, 1942, Memo to Julius, July 18, 1942; 9.
      - Felsentreger to Emspak Regarding Wages and Unemployment, October 13, 1942; 10.
      - Felsentreger to James Matles Regarding Local 259 Worthington Pump Contracts, February 1, 1943; 11.
      - Richard Gelinas to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 24, 1944; 12.
      - Ted Green to UE Regarding Local 259 Worthington Pump Contracts, August 6, 1942; 13.
      - Leon Massa to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 2, 1943; 14.
      - Massa to Emspak Regarding United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, October 22, 1945; 15.
      - Massa to Jerald Mooney Regarding 1948 UE Convention, July 20, 1948; 16.
      - Carlton Stiles to Matles Regarding Cincinnati Worthington Pumps and Espionage, February 21, 1943; 17.
      - Stiles to Emspak Regarding Mine, Mill and Smelter Strikes, March 6, 1942; 18.
      - Stiles to Nat Geller Regarding Finances, March 30, 1942; 19.
      - Stiles to Matles Regarding Wages, April 2, 1942; 20.
      - Stiles Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 259 Steel Workers Organizing Committee Contracts, April 6, 1942; 21.
      - Stiles to Matles Regarding Worthington Pump Joint Negotiations, Wages and United Steelworkers of America, April 16, 1942; 22.
      - Stiles to Matles Regarding Local 259 Worthington Pump Collective Bargaining, May 29, 1942; 23.
    - Local 259 Outgoing Correspondence, February-April 1955 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - Stephen Sutton to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Arbitration, February 1955; 1.
      - Sutton to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, April 15, 1955; 2.
    - Local 259 Correspondence, July 8, 1966-November 20, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Local 259 Salary and Expense Letters, Raymond Richards, October 9, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Local 259 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, January 16, 1957-December 29, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Local 259 Samson Firing, December 16-29, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Louis Samson to Julius Emspak, December 16, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Leonard Lewin, December 18, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak Secretary to Samson, December 18, 1942; 3.
      - Lewin to Emspak, December 29, 1942; 4.
    - Local 259 Westinghouse Married Women Leschuck vs. Leberman, August 3, 1950-February 1, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Local 259 Worthington Pump Mannix vs. Massa, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Local 259 Officers Election, January 3-March 16, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Mass Meeting Minutes, January 3, 1943; 1.
      - William McLaughlin to Julius Emspak, June 6, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Richard Linsley, January 13, 1943; 3.
      - Ballot, January 1943; 4.
      - Leon Massa to Emspak, February 5, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Charles Rivers, February 12, 1943; 6.
      - Emspak to Massa, February 12, 1943; 7.
      - Rivers to Emspak, March 16, 1943; 8.
    - Local 259 Unemployment, July 1944 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Neil Brant Memo, July 14, 1944; 1.
      - Brant to Charles Auslander, July 14, 1944; 2.
      - Brant to Richard Linsley, July 14, 1944; 3.
      - Brant to H. C. Ramsey, July 14, 1944; 4.
      - Leonard Lewin to Brant, July 18, 1944; 5.
      - Navy Press Release, July 1944; 6.
      - UE Press Release, July 1944; 7.
      - Union Program, July 1944; 8.
    - Local 259 Worthington Pump War Labor Board Case, April 3, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 53)
      - David Scribner Telegram to Jack Simon, April 3, 1945; 1.
      - Simon Telegram to Scribner, April 3, 1945; 2.
    - Local 259 Holyoke Worthington Pump, January 31, 1980-October 4, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Local 259 Holyoke Correspondence, October 31, 1956-February 7, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Local 259 Leon Massa Organizational Work, November 4, 1971-April 28, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Local 259 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, April 1, 1970-September 3, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Local 259 Correspondence, March 29, 1941-March 17, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Memo to Julius Regarding Local 259 and Constitution, March 29, 1941; 1.
      - Lewis Gill to Harry Beaver Regarding War Labor Board, Worthington Pump, United Steelworkers of America, and Local 1833, July 11, 1942; 2.
      - Ray Carreau to UE News Regarding Racism, September 19, 1942; 3.
      - Albert Olson to Frederick Livingston Regarding Finances, May 1, 1944-March 17, 1949; 4-5.
    - Local 259 Correspondence, Charles Sieukiewicz to Albert Fitzgerald with Petition, April 21, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Local 259 Correspondence and Members on Strike List, October 23, 1945-July 11, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      - Paul Seymour to Julius Emspak Regarding United Steelworkers of America Inter-Union Rivalry and Worthington Pump, October 23, 1945; 1.
      - Seymour to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 29, 1946; 2.
      - Leon Massa to John Jekot Regarding Local 213, Factionalism and Operation Dixie, March 15, 1947; 3.
      - List of J. W. Jolly Members on Strike, September 1948; 4.
      - Allan Rosenberg to David Scribner Regarding Workmans Compensation, March 30, 1951; 5.
      - Emspak to Seymour Regarding Supplies, February 21, 1952; 6.
      - Rosenberg to Massa Regarding Arbitration and Finances with November 1955, Massa Letter to Emspak, March 1, 1955; 7.
      - Scribner Memo Regarding Arbitrations and Worthington Pump, July 11, 1955; 8.
      - Unsigned Letter to Emspak Regarding Address Change, 9.
    - Local 259 Newspaper Clippings, August 11-14, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      - "CIO Council in this Area Steps into Political Field", August 11, 1942; 1.
      - "Wortihngton Employees Vote on Contract", August 14, 1942; 2.
      - "West Mass. CIO Approves FDR War Conduct", 3.
  - Local 260
    - Local 260 Officers Lists, July 25, 1941-January 19, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 62)